springloops.com 2019-08-25

# Privacy Policy - Buddy | Buddy: The DevOps Automation Platform

Privacy Policy of BDY Sp. z o. o. Sp. k., a company incorporated and registered in Poland whose registered office is at Migdałowa 4, 02-796, Warszawa referenced in this document as "Buddy". 

Buddy is the only owner of the information collected on its websites. The information we collect about visitors to our website includes the visitor’s browser type, language preference, referring site, additional websites requested, and the date and time of each visitor request. We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 

The aim of Buddy activity is not collecting, selling or lending the information to the others. We collect this information to better understand how our website visitors use Buddy, and to monitor and protect the security of the website. We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties for their commercial purposes. 

We do not intentionally collect sensitive personal information, such as social security numbers, genetic data, health information, or religious information. Although Buddy does not request or intentionally collect any sensitive personal information, we realize that you might store this kind of information in your account, such as in a repository. If you store any sensitive personal information on our servers, you are consenting to our storage of that information on our servers, which are in the United States. 

We may share your personal information with your permission, so we can perform services you have requested. 

We do not host advertising on Buddy. We may occasionally embed content from third-party sites, such as YouTube, Vimeo, or Disqus, and that content may include ads. While we try to minimize the number of ads our embedded content contains, we cant always control what third parties show. 

We may share User Personal Information with a limited number of third-party vendors who process it on our behalf to provide or improve our service, and who have agreed to privacy restrictions similar to our own Privacy Statement. Our vendors perform services such as payment processing (Braintree), customer support ticketing (Intercom), network data transmission, and other similar services. When we transfer your data to our vendors under Privacy Shield, we remain responsible for it. 

Registration & Accounts  
To create a workspace (account) in Buddy, we will ask you for a valid email address. Such information is necessary to use the Service in a proper way by the user who got interested in this Service themself. 

Once you register, you also have the option to give us more information if you want to in your profile settings, and this may include personal information. Personal information is any information about one of our users which could, alone or together with other information, personally identify him or her. Information such as a username and password, an email address, a real name, and a photograph are examples of personal information. This information is only available for you and other members of the workspace (account), unless you explicitly decide to share, e.g. using third-party integrations such as Slack notifications. 

We need your personal information, specifically your email address, to send you password reset forms, billing information, and messages about items followed in the workspace (account), such as deployment notifications. 

Personal Information does not include aggregated, non-personally identifying information. We may use aggregated, non-personally identifying information to operate, improve, and optimize our website and service. 

You must be at least 13 years old to use the Service. Buddy does not knowingly collect information from or direct any of our content specifically to children under 13. If we learn or have reason to suspect that you are a user who is under the age of 13, we will have to close your account. 

The assurance of privacy, safety and integrity of the entrusted data of their Clients is one of the most important goals of Buddy. In regard to that Buddy is not going to sell, lend and trade contractual data as well as the data of registered accounts. 

We limit our use of your personal information to the purposes listed in this Privacy Statement. If we need to use it for other purposes, we will ask your permission first. 

Cookies are series of data stored on the hard disk of the user which for example include the anonymous identifier of the user. The cookies are set up to remember the fact of being logged in the Service if the user wished so as well as for statistical aims. By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your computer or device. If you disable your browser or device’s ability to accept cookies, you will not be able to log in or use Buddy’s services. 

Certain pages on our site may set other third-party cookies. For example, we may embed content, such as videos, from another site that sets a cookie. While we try to minimize these third-party cookies, we can’t always control what cookies this third-party content sets. 

We use Google Analytics as a third-party tracking service, but we don’t use it to track you individually or collect personal user information. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how our website performs and how our users, in general, navigate through and use Buddy. This helps us evaluate our users’ use of Buddy, compile statistical reports on activity, and improve our content and website performance. 

Google Analytics gathers certain simple, non-personally identifying information over time, such as your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring and exit pages, timestamp, and similar data about your use of Buddy. We do not link this information to any of your personal information such as your username. 

Buddy will not, nor will we allow any third-party to, use the Google Analytics tool to track our users individually, collect any personal information other than IP address; or correlate your IP address with your identity. Google provides further information about its own privacy practices and offers a browser add-on to opt out of Google Analytics tracking. 

If you do not want online services to collect and share certain kinds of information about your online activity from third-party tracking services, you can set the Do Not Track privacy preference in your browser. 

We do not track your online browsing activity on other online services over time and we do not permit third-party services to track your activity on our site with the exception of basic Google Analytics tracking and occasional user behavior tracking performed with Hotjar analytics tool. The tracking data is collected exclusively to improve the UX and performance of the Service and website. Buddy does not record any personal data with Hotjar as all text entered to the Service during tracking is suppressed before the data is sent back to Hotjar servers. 

Because we do not share this kind of data with third-party services or permit this kind of third-party data collection on Buddy for any of our users, and we do not track our users on third-party websites ourselves, we do not need to respond differently to an individual browsers Do Not Track setting. If you wish, you can opt out from Google Analytics tracking here, and from Hotjar here. 

Buddy uses certain vendors in providing its Services. All services either fully comply with GDPR regulations or are to implement it shortly.  
Our emails might contain a pixel tag, which is a small, clear image that can tell us whether or not you have opened an email and what your IP address is. We use this pixel tag to make our email more effective for you and to make sure we’re not sending you unwanted email. If you prefer not to receive pixel tags, please opt out of marketing emails. 

  * **[Amazon Web Services](https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/all-aws-services-gdpr-ready/)** – hosting infrastructure for the Service and SES for email and SMS notifications (United States)
  * **[Braintree](https://www.braintreepayments.com/blog/getting-gdpr-ready/)** – payment processing (United States)
  * **[DigitalOcean](https://www.digitalocean.com/security/gdpr/)** – hosting infrastructure for Buddy’s website (United States)
  * **[Google G Suite](https://cloud.google.com/security/gdpr/)** – email communication with clients (United States)
  * **[Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/gdpr-commitment)** – UX analytics (EU/Malta)
  * **[Intercom](https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/data-protection/how-were-preparing-for-gdpr)** – helpdesk and customer messaging platform (United States)
  * **[SingleHop](https://www.singlehop.com/legal/eu-data-privacy/)** – parts of hosting infrastructure for the Service (until May 2018) (United States)

Buddy uses Amazon Web Services to store client data and DigitalOcean as hosting infrastructure for the Services website. Physical servers for both services are located in the United States. 

All data uploaded by the Users belong to the Users. Buddy does not claim any rights to intellectual property uploaded by the Users. 

Despite that Buddy hosts all data entered by the user, the ones all the time belong to the user. Buddy will never sell or by purpose make accessible the data entered by the user to the third-party as well as will never use them for the benefit of his own business. Our procedures obey the privacy of our users and their data. 

Unless you notify Buddy otherwise in writing, You hereby grant to Buddy and its wholly owned subsidiaries a limited license to use Your trade names, trademarks, service marks, logos, domain names and other distinctive brand features in presentations, marketing materials, websites, customer lists, and financial reports. 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire to access or use the Service, you may correct, update, amend or delete it by contacting our customer support team at **[support@buddy.works](mailto:support@buddy.works)**

That said, where Buddy’s customer for the Service is an organization and a user is accessing and using the Service as an authorized representative of that organization, references to “you” and the like in this Privacy Policy generally refer to the customer organization, not individual end users. In such cases, Buddy receives and processes information under the direction of its customer and has no direct contractual relationship with the individuals whose personal information is or may be provided. Any such individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his or her query to the applicable Buddy customer and we will respond to the customer’s request within a reasonable timeframe. 

Information that we collect will be stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Statement. However, we understand that we have users from different countries and regions with different privacy expectations, and we try to meet those needs. 

We provide the same standard of privacy protection to all our users around the world with the same levels of notice, choice, accountability, security, data integrity, access, and recourse, regardless of their country of origin or location. We work hard to comply with the applicable data privacy laws wherever we do business. Additionally, we require that if our vendors or affiliates have access to personal information, they must comply with our privacy policies and with applicable data privacy laws, including signing data transfer agreements. 

  * Buddy provides clear methods of unambiguous, informed consent at the time of data collection, when we do collect your personal data.
  * We collect only the minimum amount of personal data necessary, unless you choose to provide more. We do not encourage you to give us more data than you are comfortable sharing.
  * We offer you simple methods of accessing, correcting, or deleting the data we have collected.
  * We provide our users notice, choice, accountability, security, and access, and we limit the purpose for processing. These are the Privacy Shield Principles, that Buddy fully adheres. In addition to providing our users methods of unambiguous, informed consent and control over their data, we participate in and comply with the Privacy Shield framework, and we are committed to subject any personal information we receive from the EU and EEA to the Privacy Shield Principles.
  * We also comply with the principles of the Safe Harbor Framework for Swiss data transfers to the US.

Buddy discloses potentially personal information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (1) need to know that information in order to process it on Buddy’s behalf or to provide services available in connection with the Service and (2) have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Buddy’s Website and/or the Service, you consent to the transfer of information to such individuals and organizations in order to support our provision to you of the Website and the Service. These supporting partners may be authorized to, for example, process payments on our behalf or provide customer support. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our customers. However, in each case, these partners are authorized to use your personally identifying information only as necessary to provide the services we request. 

Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, Buddy discloses personal information only when required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process, or when Buddy believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Buddy, third parties, or the public at large. If Buddy is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, either you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice through the Service of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifying information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information or we will require any such buyer to agree to treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

If you are a registered user of the Service and have supplied your email address, Buddy may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Buddy and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Buddy takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information. 

Buddy doesn’t ask for more personal data from our users than we need to provide our services to you. We provide you the ability to access and delete the data you have given us (e.g. you can remove your profile information at any time). If you want to erase all personal information that we have about you, please send a request to **[support@buddy.works](mailto:support@buddy.works)**. We have gone through our Privacy Statement to provide more context and transparency, though, so our users understand exactly why we ask for information and what we’ll do with it. 

If we are going to change our Privacy Policy we will inform our users about this fact, by sending an appropriate email to the email address of the owner’s account registered in our Service.
